# **Arun BS**

## Software Engineer III

#### Personal Info

#### Address:

26/b, 13th Cross Road, Pragathi Layout,

Doddanekundi

Bangalore - 560037

Phone:

9739185574

E-mail:

bsarunmca@gmail.com

Date of birth:

1989-10-30

Portfolio:

https://bsarunmca.github.io/

#### **Skills**

React JS, Redux

JavaScript, ES6

jQuery

NodeJS

Webpack

Python

Angular JS (1.x)

AJAX, JSON

HTML, HTML5

CSS, CSS3, SCSS

Bootstrap

Lesshint, JSInspect

### Achievements

#### Toshiba:

~ Worked at Japan for technical collaboration and establishing communication bridge between teams

~ Award wining project in a Tech fare at Toshiba : WebPanel Style Guide. This project is a toolkit for developing the MFP UI.

### Payoda:

~ SPOT award for New tool exploration and helping the team

~ SPOT award for fixing critical issue

Creative front-end developer with 7+ years of work experience in developing web applications and embedded applications as per W3 Standards. Onsite experience(Japan) to discuss the architecture and planning for the upcoming projects of MFP and support MSM and TSIP. Team player with good listening skills and innovative ideas to make attractive designs and development. Good exposure to AGILE and SCRUM methodologies.

### **Experience**

2019-12 - **Software Engineer III** 

present NCR Corporation

**Money Movement** 

Tech stack: ReactJS, Redux, GCP, Webpack, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JSON, MUI,

GIT, etc...

**Description**: NCR Digital Banking is a provider of online banking software to banks and credit unions. My role and responsibility is to lead a team and develop UI for 'US'

banking applications on Payee, Payment, Template and Report module etc.

2017-11 - **Senior Software Engineer** 

2019-12 Toshiba Software India Private Limted

**WebPanel** 

**Tech stack**: ReactJS, Redux, ESLint, Python, HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, JavaScript **Description**: Toshiba Printer has an embedded browser for MFP (Multi Functional printers). My role is to develop UI for MFP. Traveled Japan(Onsite) to discuss the architecture and planning for the upcoming modules and establish a communication bridge between Toshiba MSM and Toshiba TSIP.

2015-12 - Software Engineer

2017-11 Payoda Technologies

Arista CVP

**Tech stack**: HTML5, CSS3, Angularjs, jQuery, d3js, Requirejs, AJAX, JSON, NPM, Grunt, ESLint, Lesshint, JSInspect, Jasmine.

**Description**: CLOUDVISION is a central portal for managing all the network switches making it easier to configure and monitor better than ever. CVP combines a front-end web-based dashboard for performing the pre-integrated operational workflows and a backend state repository and analytics engine for maintaining historic network state.

2014-07 - Frontend Developer

2015-11 Sakhatech Information Systems Pvt. Ltd

TNT, Tellofy

Tech stack: CSS3, Bootstrap 3.0, JQuery, AJAX, JSON, Facebook API, Google plus

API, Twiter API, & Linkedin API

**Description**: Web applications for shipping company.

TNT - Customer, TNT - Customer Care, TNT - PUD(Purchase and delivery details)

### Education

2010 - Erode Arts and Science College

2013 • MCA - Master of Computer Application

2006 - Jairam Arts & Science College

• BSc - Maths with Computer Application